http://alexkelly.biz/privacy-policy/

Products by age group
Primary School (4-10)
Secondary School (11-16)
Special Schools (4-16)
Adult (16+)
Privacy Policy
We want our customers and visitors to be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Information Collection and Use
We respect each site visitor’s right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.
For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically collects visitor information and IP addressThe information we collect is never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes and is only used by Alex Kelly Ltd to analyse website statistics for our own development.
Registration is not required to enter our site.
We require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address). If we have trouble processing an order, we use the information to contact the user. This information is used for shipping and billing purposes and to complete customer´s orders. We do not store financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date) – this information is sent directly to PayPal Ltd through Secure Socket Layers.
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors of this feature through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
We publish a newsletter, and we never sell or share our subscribers’ email addresses.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.
Conflict Resolution
We are committed to resolving disputes within 48 hours. If problems arise, users may contact us by email or telephone.
Contact Information
If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using the contact form on this site
Recent Posts
Social Skills Training in 2021
Contact Us
Please send us an email and we'll get back to you.
